gretathemes.com 2018-04-17

# Privacy Policy ⋆ GretaThemes

Your privacy is critically important to us. At GretaThemes we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

It is GretaThemes’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, GretaThemes collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. GretaThemes’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how GretaThemes’s visitors use its website. From time to time, GretaThemes may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

GretaThemes also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog. GretaThemes only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to GretaThemes’s websites choose to interact with GretaThemes in ways that require GretaThemes to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that GretaThemes gathers depend on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who purchase a product at [gretathemes.com](http://gretathemes.com/) to provide their name, a username, and an email address. GretaThemes collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with GretaThemes. GretaThemes does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

GretaThemes may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. GretaThemes may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, GretaThemes does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

GretaThemes discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GretaThemes’s behalf or to provide services available at GretaThemes’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using GretaThemes’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GretaThemes will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, GretaThemes discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when GretaThemes believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GretaThemes, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of GretaThemes website and have supplied your email address, GretaThemes may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GretaThemes and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GretaThemes takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GretaThemes uses cookies to help GretaThemes identify and track visitors, their usage of GretaThemes website, and their website access preferences. GretaThemes visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GretaThemes’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of GretaThemes’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If GretaThemes, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GretaThemes goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that are transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and that any acquirer of GretaThemes may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, GretaThemes may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GretaThemes’s sole discretion. GretaThemes encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
